A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 5, 1939-1983; 5; 33.22 Cubic Feet 82 letter document boxes, 4 legal document boxes, and 1 half-letter document box.
  - Boschert, Inc. - Financials, 1977-1980 (Box 446, Folder 4, Box 447, Folder 1-4, Box 448, Folder 1-2, Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Boschert, Inc. - General, 1977-1980 (Box 448, Folder 3, Box 449, Folder 2-3)
  - Boschert, Inc. - Shareholders, Stockholders, 1977-1980 (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Qantel Corporation - Financing, 1978 (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - Qantel Corporation - Board of Directors, 1979-1980 (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Qantel Corporation - Financial, 1974-1980 (Box 450, Folder 4)
  - Qantel Corporation - General, 1979-1980 (Box 450, Folder 5)
  - Qantel Corporation - Shareholders, 1979 (Box 450, Folder 6)
  - Boston Partners, 1970-1975 (Box 450, Folder 7)
  - CCI Corporation - Annual Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 465, Folder 4)
  - CCI Corporation - Agreements (Box 466, Folder 1)
  - CCI Corporation - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 466, Folder 2)
  - CCI Corporation - Board of Directors Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 466, Folder 3)
  - CCI Corporation - Financial, 1972-1977 (Box 466, Folder 4)
  - CCI Corporation - General, 1968-1978 (Box 466, Folder 5)
  - CCI Corporation - General - Peter O. Crisp (POC) comments, 1976 (Box 466, Folder 6)
  - CCI Corporation - Marketing, 1976-1978 (Box 466, Folder 7)
  - CCI Corporation - Mergers - CCI Life Systems, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 467, Folder 1)
  - CCI Corporation - Mergers - Marquardt Corp., 1949-1969 (Box 467, Folder 2)
  - CCI Corporation - Mergers - Safetran Systems Corp., 1971-1977 (Box 467, Folder 3)
  - CCI Corporation - Stockholders, 1965-1978 (Box 466, Folder 8)
  - Coherent Radiation, Inc. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1968-1978 (Box 468, Folder 1-2)
  - Coherent Radiation, Inc. - Financing, 1967-1971; 1971 June (Box 468, Folder 3-4, Box 469, Folder 1-3)
  - Coherent Radiation, Inc. - Stock Power Transfer - Colonial Williamsburg to Pocantico, 1976 (Box 469, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Property Investors - Purchase Agreement, 1971 (Box 451, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Property Investors - Annual Reports, 1974-1979 (Box 451, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Property Investors - Financials, 1976-1978 (Box 451, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Property Investors - General, 1967-1979 (Box 451, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Property Investors - Offering Circular, 1971-1975 (Box 452, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Property Investors - Shareholders, 1972-1980 (Box 452, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Property Investors - Stock Options, 1976-1977 (Box 451, Folder 5)
  - DSV Associates - Liquidation of Data Science Ventures, 1975-1976 (Box 469, Folder 5)
  - DSV Associates - Financing, 1974 June (Box 469, Folder 6-7)
  - DSV Associates - Summary of Activities, 1976-1978 (Box 470, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Agreement - LSR, 1967 (Box 470, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Agreement - Mutual Aid, 1975 (Box 470, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Advisory Council, 1968-1975 (Box 470, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Anti Dilution Provisions, 1967-1970 (Box 470, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws, 1957-1978 (Box 470, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Executive Committee Meetings, 1974-1977 (Box 470, Folder 7-8)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Financial Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box 471, Folder 1-2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Financing L-1011 Aircraft, 1974 (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Financing, 1973 (Box 471, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Supplemental Indentures - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 471, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Supplemental Indentures - Mortgage, 1963 October 1; 1974-1977 (Box 471, Folder 6, Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Financing - 1963-1968 - 5 3/8 Convertible Subordinated Notes (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - General, 1964-1982 (Box 472, Folder 3-4, Box 473, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - LSR Interest, 1939-1978 (Box 473, Folder 2-3)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Marketing, 1978 (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Mergers, 1967-1980 (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Mergers - Allegheny Air Lines, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Mergers - Caribbean Atlantic Air Lines, 1971-1975 (Box 474, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Prospectus, 1965-1977 (Box 474, Folder 4-5)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Public Relations, 1962-1975 (Box 475, Folder 1-2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Rolls Royce, 1971-1977 (Box 475, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Shareholders, 1939-1976 (Box 475, Folder 4-5)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Stock Options, 1942-1966 (Box 476, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Trans Pacific Route Case, 1968 (Box 476, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Trans Pacific Route Decision (Robert L. Park), 1967-1968 (Box 476, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Trans Pacific Route Investigation, 1949-1964 (Box 476, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Trans Pacific Route Investigation, 1967-1969 (Box 477, Folder 1-2)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - LSR - Review of Holdings, 1976-1980 (Box 525, Folder 3-4)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - LSR Interests, 1976-1978 (Box 525, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Airlines, Inc. - Negotiations with Eastern Airlines - Peter O. Crisp (POC) Workpapers, 1976-1977 (Box 526, Folder 1-2)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - Agreement - Investment Agreement, 1975 (Box 477, Folder 3)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - Agreement - Note Purchase Agreement, 1970-1978 (Box 478, Folder 1)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - Financial, 1976-1977 (Box 477, Folder 4)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - Financing - 7 and one-half Convertible Note, 1975-1978 (Box 477, Folder 5)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - Financing - Investment Memo, 1975 June (Box 478, Folder 2)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - General, 1972-1980 (Box 478, Folder 3)
  - Eberline Instrument Corp. - Mergers - Thermo Electron, 1979 (Box 478, Folder 4)
  - Energy Conversion Devices, Inc., 1968-1978 (Box 452, Folder 3)
  - Envirogas Drilling Program, 1977-1978 (Box 478, Folder 5)
  - Ethyl Corp. - Legal Documents, 1962 (Box 479, Folder 1)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Investment Agreements, 1976 (Box 478, Folder 6)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Purchase Agreement, 1972 October 20 (Box 478, Folder 7)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Agreement - Silver King Mines, 1969-1971 (Box 479, Folder 2)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 478, Folder 8)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Board of Directors Meetings, 1970-1979 (Box 479, Folder 3-4, Box 480, Folder 1-2)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financial - Audits, 1969-1978 (Box 480, Folder 3)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financial - Correspondence and Reviews, 1971-1978 (Box 481, Folder 1)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financial - Statements, 1977-1979 (Box 481, Folder 2)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing, 1974 January (Box 481, Folder 3)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing - GCA Note, 1973 (Box 481, Folder 4)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing, 1972 October-November (Box 481, Folder 5)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing - Investment Memo, 1972 (Box 481, Folder 6)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing - Sub Notes, 1971 March (Box 481, Folder 7)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing - Sub Note, 1969 June 15 (Box 481, Folder 8)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing, 1970 December (Box 482, Folder 1)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Financing, 1968 August 20 (Box 482, Folder 2)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - General, 1970-1979 (Box 482, Folder 3)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Merger Prospects, 1978 (Box 482, Folder 4)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Mergers - Applicon, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 482, Folder 5)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Mergers - GCA, 1972 (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Redifon Electronics, Inc. (Box 483, Folder 1)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Redifon Electronics, Inc. - Financing, 1975 (Box 483, Folder 2)
  - Evans and Sutherland Computer Corporation - Stockholders, 1968-1977 (Box 483, Folder 3)
  - First Harlem Securities - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - First Harlem Securities - Financial, 1972-1975 (Box 484, Folder 2)
  - First Harlem Securities - Financing, 1973-1974 (Box 484, Folder 3)
  - First Jersey National Bank, 1965-1979 (Box 484, Folder 4)
  - Friday Computers - Board of Directors, 1981-1982 (Box 484, Folder 5)
  - Friday Computers - General, 1981 (Box 484, Folder 6)
  - Friday Computers - Financing, 1981 (Box 485, Folder 1-3)
  - GCA, 1959-1974 (Box 485, Folder 4)
  - Global Marine Inc., 1964-1980 (Box 485, Folder 5)
  - Greenwich Oil Corp., 1972-1976 (Box 486, Folder 1)
  - Harken Oil and Gas, 1978-1979 (Box 486, Folder 2)
  - Hazen Research, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 486, Folder 3)
  - IBEC - Annual Reports, 1966-1977 (Box 486, Folder 4, Box 487, Folder 1)
  - IBEC - Anderson Division, 1976-1979 (Box 487, Folder 2)
  - IBEC - Arbor Acres, 1976-1979 (Box 487, Folder 3, Box 488, Folder 1)
  - IBEC - Bellows International Division, 1977-1978 (Box 488, Folder 2)
  - IBEC - Board of Directors, 1973-1976 (Box 488, Folder 3-4)
  - IBEC - Board of Directors, 1977-1978 (Box 489, Folder 1-3)
  - IBEC - Corporate Reorganization, 1978-1979 (Box 489, Folder 4)
  - IBEC - Financial - Audits, 1973-1978 (Box 490, Folder 1)
  - IBEC - Financial - Audit Committee Meetings, 1974-1979 (Box 490, Folder 2-3, Box 491, Folder 1-2)
  - IBEC - Financial - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 491, Folder 3)
  - IBEC - Financial - Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 491, Folder 4)
  - IBEC - General, 1962-1979 (Box 492, Folder 1-2)
  - IBEC - IMCO, 1977-1978 (Box 492, Folder 3)
  - IBEC - Meetings, 1972-1978 (Box 492, Folder 4)
  - IBEC - Puerto Rican Housing Project, 1977 (Box 493, Folder 1)
  - Inforex - General, 1970-1978 (Box 503, Folder 3)
  - Inforex - Private Placement - Convertible Debentures, 1969-1976 (Box 503, Folder 4)
  - Intel Corporation - Annual Reports, 1972-1978 (Box 504, Folder 1)
  - Intel Corporation - Financials, 1974-1978 (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Intel Corporation - General, 1970-1979 (Box 504, Folder 3)
  - Intel Corporation - SEC, 1973-1975 (Box 504, Folder 4)
  - Intel Corporation - Stock Distribution, 1975 October 27 (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Intel Corporation - Stock Distribution, 1976 February 27 (Box 504, Folder 6)
  - Intel Corporation - Stock, 1975 (Box 504, Folder 7)
  - Interpool Ltd., 1977 (Box 504, Folder 8)
  - Interstate United, 1969-1977 (Box 504, Folder 9)
  - Itek Corporation - Annual Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 505, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corporation - By-Laws, Certificate of Incorporation, 1960-1976 (Box 504, Folder 10)
  - Itek Corporation - Board of Directors Correspondence, 1958-1977 (Box 505, Folder 2)
  - Itek Corporation - Board of Directors Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 505, Folder 3-4, Box 506, Folder 1-3)
  - Itek Corporation - Shareholders Meetings, 1958-1966 (Box 506, Folder 4)
  - Itek Corporation - Family Stock Sale, 1959-1965 (Box 506, Folder 5)
  - Itek Corporation - Financing, 1957-1960; 1964-1966 (Box 507, Folder 1-5)
  - Itek Corporation - Finance and Audit Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 508, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corporation - Financial - Audits, 1968-1975 (Box 508, Folder 2)
  - Itek Corporation - Financial - Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box 508, Folder 3)
  - Itek Corporation - Financial - Statements, 1979 (Box 508, Folder 4-5)
  - Itek Corporation - Financial - SEC, 1965-1976 (Box 509, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corporation - General, 1975-1979 (Box 509, Folder 2)
  - Itek Corporation - Mergers, 1973-1978 (Box 509, Folder 3-4)
  - Itek Corporation - Mergers - Applied Technology, 1967-1978 (Box 510, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corporation - Nominating Committee, 1979 July 2 (Box 510, Folder 2)
  - Itek Corporation - Funds Evaluation Service, 1977-1979 (Box 510, Folder 3)
  - Itek Corporation - Pension Plan, 1961-1979 (Box 510, Folder 4, Box 511, Folder 1-3)
  - Itek Corporation - Pension Plan - Advisory Review, 1977-1978 (Box 511, Folder 4-5)
  - Itek Corporation - Financial Forecast, 1960-1963 (Box 513, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corporation - Prospectus, 1966-1978 (Box 512, Folder 1)
  - Itek Corporation - SEC, 1976-1978 (Box 512, Folder 2)
  - Itek Corporation - Compensation, 1959-1974 (Box 512, Folder 3)
  - Itek Corporation - Stock Option Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 512, Folder 4)
  - Itek Corporation - Shareholders, Stockholders Meetings, 1958-1978 (Box 512, Folder 5-6)
  - Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) (Box 512, Folder 7)
  - Jim Walter Corporation - Purchase Agreement, 1969-1971 (Box 513, Folder 2)
  - Jim Walter Corporation - General, 1972-1978 (Box 513, Folder 3)
  - LearTek Corporation, 1975-1980 (Box 452, Folder 4)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Loan Agreements, 1973 (Box 514, Folder 1)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Agreements, 1971-1972 (Box 514, Folder 2-3)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Purchase Agreement, 1969 (Box 513, Folder 4)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Agreement - Lyman, 1977 (Box 513, Folder 5)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - AEA Investment Memo (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Annual Reports, Shareholders, Prospectus, 1969-1977 (Box 515, Folder 2)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Financials, 1970-1978 (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Financial Reports, 1971-1978 (Box 515, Folder 4)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Financing, 1975 (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Financing 1973 - Debt Extension (Box 516, Folder 1)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Financing 1973 - Trade Creditor Agreement - Bank Loan Agreement (Box 516, Folder 2)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - General, 1969-1979 (Box 516, Folder 3)
  - Leisure Group Inc. - Yard Man Inc., 1971 (Box 514, Folder 4)
  - Linwood Development Corporation, 1963-1980 (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - Magnuson Computer Systems - Financing - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Magnuson Computer Systems - Financing, 1977-1979 (Box 517, Folder 1)
  - Magnuson Computer Systems - Financials, 1978-1980 (Box 518, Folder 5)
  - Magnuson Computer Systems - Product Literature, Brochures, 1980-1981 (Box 517, Folder 2)
  - McDonnell Douglas Corp. - Lawsuit - Eastern Airlines, 1970 (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Closing 1978 - Liquidating Distribution 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 518, Folder 1)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Business Plan, 1977-1980 (Box 518, Folder 2)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Financial - Audits, 1975-1979 (Box 518, Folder 3)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Financial, 1976-1979 (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Financing, 1977 June 28 (Box 519, Folder 1)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - Financing - Promissory Note, 1976-1979 (Box 519, Folder 2)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - General, 1977-1979 (Box 519, Folder 3)
  - Mediscan, Inc. - General Electric Co., Ltd., 1979 (Box 519, Folder 4)
  - Mediscan,Inc. - Mergers, 1979 (Box 520, Folder 1)
  - Mediscan,Inc. - Mergers - Smith Kline, 1979-1980 (Box 520, Folder 2)
  - Mediscan,Inc. - Mergers - Xerox, 1977-1979 (Box 520, Folder 3)
  - Mediscan,Inc. - Shareholders, 1977-1980 (Box 520, Folder 4)
  - Mediscan,Inc. - Stock Options, 1978 (Box 520, Folder 5)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Agreements, 1977-1978 (Box 521, Folder 1)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Shares, 1978 July (Box 521, Folder 2)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1972-1978 (Box 521, Folder 3)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Financial - Audits, 1970-1972 (Box 521, Folder 4)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Financials, 1970-1978 (Box 521, Folder 5)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Financing, 1970 (Box 521, Folder 6-7)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Public Offering, Prospectus, 1972-1977 (Box 522, Folder 1)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - Shareholders, Stockholders, 1970-1978 (Box 522, Folder 2)
  - New England Business Service, Inc. - SEC, 1976-1977 (Box 523, Folder 1)
  - Omega Fund, 1974-1979 (Box 523, Folder 2)
  - Orion Capital Corporation, 1972-1981 (Box 453, Folder 1)
    Name changed from Equity Funding Corp. in 1976.
  - Palant, Lyle Robert, 1976-1977 (Box 522, Folder 3)
  - Penn Central Corp. - Penn Central Transporation, 1973-1976 (Box 523, Folder 3-4)
  - Petrolero Corporation, 1973-1979 (Box 522, Folder 4)
  - Pickands Mather, 1966-1980 (Box 524, Folder 1)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Summary, 1972 (Box 453, Folder 2)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Cornelius H. Borman (CHB) file, 1972-1979 (Box 453, Folder 3)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Investment Agreements, 1969-1972 (Box 453, Folder 4)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreements - Commerical Research Corp., 1969 (Box 453, Folder 5)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreements - Foothill Group, 1970-1975 (Box 453, Folder 6)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreements - McCarty Company, 1970 (Box 453, Folder 7)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreements - Thermo Electron, 1974-1978 (Box 453, Folder 8)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreements - Thermo Electron - Agreements - Financing, 1972 July (Box 454, Folder 1)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreement - Thermo Electron - Patent, Equipment, Sublease, 1970s (Box 454, Folder 2)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1972 (Box 454, Folder 3)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box 454, Folder 4)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1967-1978 (Box 454, Folder 5)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Peter O. Crisp (POC) Notes, Contacts, 1974 (Box 454, Folder 6)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Financial - Audits, 1967-1978 (Box 454, Folder 7)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Financial - Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 455, Folder 1)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Financing, 1968-1979 (Box 455, Folder 2-6)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Public Offering - Prospectus, 1972 September (Box 456, Folder 1)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Public Offering - Correspondence, 1972 September (Box 456, Folder 2)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - General, 1967-1975 (Box 456, Folder 3-4)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - C.B. Smith Correspondence re: "Asenco", 1969 (Box 456, Folder 5)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Merger Conversation, 1977-1979 (Box 456, Folder 6)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Patents, 1972-1976 (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Sprague Electric Company, 1970-1971 (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Shareholders, Stockholders, 1969-1979 (Box 457, Folder 2-3)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Stock Option, 1969-1981 (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Pocantico Fund, 1975-1979 (Box 524, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - International City Corp., 1972-1973 (Box 526, Folder 3-4)
  - Real Estate - International City Corp., 1973-1979 (Box 527, Folder 1-2)
  - Robertson Research International, 1978-1979 (Box 524, Folder 3)
  - Scan Data Corporation, 1969-1979 (Box 525, Folder 1)
  - Shur Medical Corporation, 1973-1980 (Box 525, Folder 2)
  - Siltec Corporation, 1979-1980 (Box 527, Folder 3)
  - Solarex Corporation, 1978-1980 (Box 527, Folder 4)
  - Stratigraphic Resources, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 527, Folder 5)
  - Takara Partners, 1974-1978 (Box 528, Folder 1)
  - Tartan Production Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 528, Folder 2)
  - Taylor and Company (Arthur Taylor), 1979 (Box 528, Folder 3)
  - Texfi Industries, Inc., 1965-1976 (Box 457, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agreement - Voting Trust Agreement, 1977 (Box 528, Folder 4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agreement - Purchase Agreement, 1966-1969 (Box 528, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agreement - Aegeus Shipping Co., 1975 (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agreement - Cal Doran, 1971 (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agreement - First National Bank of Boston, 1975 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Agreement - Mass. Mutual Life Insurance, 1977 (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Annual Reports, 1968-1978 (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 529, Folder 6)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 529, Folder 7, Box 530, Folder 1-2)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Compensation, 1962-1977 (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Financial - Audits, 1960-1974 (Box 530, Folder 4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Financial - Audit Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 530, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Financial, 1962-1979 (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Financing, 1960-1969 (Box 531, Folder 2-4, Box 532, Folder 1-3)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Summary, 1967 (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Ford Motor Company, 1968-1974 (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - General, 1969-1979 (Box 532, Folder 6, Box 533, Folder 1-4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Marketing, 1969-1978 (Box 533, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Mergers - General, 1977 (Box 534, Folder 1)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Mergers - General, 1970-1973 (Box 534, Folder 2)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Nuclear Heart, 1971-1975 (Box 534, Folder 3)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Prospectus, 1967-1974 (Box 534, Folder 4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Prospectus - Exchange Offer - Lodding Engineering, 1969 December 24 (Box 534, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - SEC, 1968-1979 (Box 535, Folder 1-2)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Steam Engine, 1973 (Box 535, Folder 3)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Stock Option Committee Meetings, 1961-1975 (Box 535, Folder 4)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Stock Options, 1960-1978 (Box 535, Folder 5)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Stockholders, 1961-1979 (Box 535, Folder 6)
  - Thermo Electron Corp. - Stockholders Meetings, 1960-1978 (Box 536, Folder 1)
  - Tidelands Limited, 1979 (Box 536, Folder 2)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - General, 1958-1972 (Box 536, Folder 3)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Annual Reports, Interims, Proxy Statements, 1976-1978 (Box 536, Folder 4)
  - Valtec Corporation, 1976-1978 (Box 537, Folder 1)
  - Venture Capital - General, 1949-1982 (Box 537, Folder 2-3)
  - Venture Capital - LSR Holdings, 1951-1975 (Box 537, Folder 4)
  - Venture Capital - Small Business Administration, 1965-1978 (Box 537, Folder 5)
  - Venture Capital - Summary, 1948 (Box 537, Folder 6)
  - Venture Capital - RBI Venture Capital Investments - All Principals, 1948-1950 (Box 537, Folder 7)
  - Wagner Woodlands and Company, 1975-1979 (Box 538, Folder 1-2)
  - Wagner Woodlands and Company - Yorkshire Timber Co., Ltd., 1977 (Box 538, Folder 3)
  - T. F. Walkowicz, 1973-1979 (Box 538, Folder 4)
  - Warburg, S. G., 1965-1980 (Box 538, Folder 5)
  - Wind Energy (Windmills), 1974-1977 (Box 538, Folder 6)
  - Winrock Development Co., 1978 (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Winrock Enterprises, Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 539, Folder 2)
  - Winrock Farms, Inc. - General, 1975-1979 (Box 539, Folder 3, Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Yankee Refineries (Peter Booras), 1976-1977 (Box 540, Folder 2-4, Box 541, Folder 1)
- RBI Management and Investment Policy, 1941-1985; 6; 12.7 Cubic Feet 26 letter document boxes and 6 legal document boxes.
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Check List - Active Projects, 1948 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Incoming Mail List, 1960-1966 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws, 1948-1958 (Box 249, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Reports to Directors, 1947-1955; 1958-1960 (Box 249, Folder 9, Box 250, Folder 1-4, Box 251)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - LSR Memoranda, 1954-1962 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Investment Meetings - Aviation, 1947-1951 (Box 252, Folder 2)